alpari.com 2014-02-09

# Privacy Policy | Alpari UK

### Commitment

The privacy of our website users, whether you are our former or existing client or visitor to our website (the “Site”), is important to us and Alpari (UK) Ltd (“Alpari UK”) is committed to safeguard it. This policy demonstrates how we collect, use and protect the personal information we hold about you.

### Data collection

Alpari UK will only collect personal data when you specifically and knowingly provide it to us. If you open a Live or Demo account, you will be asked for information regarding your name and address, employment and salary details. As part of the current anti-money laundering regulations, we are required to establish proof of your identity and address details. This process may be conducted using information provided by identification verification agencies and you may be asked to supply additional information to support any unsuccessful verification attempts.

We may use the personal information you provide to contact you in the future about Alpari UK products and/or services, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes. We will also use data held on you for the purposes of (i) ensuring the content on the Site is presented in the most effective manner, (ii) carrying out our obligations arising from any agreements entered into between Alpari UK and you, and (iii) notifying you about changes to our products and/or services.

### Retention of records

Alpari UK will keep personal data only as long as it is necessary, including for the purposes of updating the product or services or as required by law. When the personal data is no longer required, it will be destroyed either by shredding or other approved destruction methods to prevent unauthorised parties from gaining access to the information during and after the process.

We will safeguard information in our custody.

We have developed and will maintain security procedures to safeguard personal data against loss, theft, copying and unauthorised disclosure, use or modification. Access to personal data is restricted to employees and authorised service providers who need it to perform their work.

### Cookies

#### What are cookies?

Cookies are small pieces of information sent by a web server to store on a web browser so it can be read back later from that web browser. Cookies may be used on some pages of the Site for us to provide Site users with a more customised web browsing experience.

### Third parties and third party links

We may provide your Personal Data to the following third parties who are not our partners, agents or affiliates:

  * person or company who provides certain services to us and you;
  * person or company who may take over certain rights and/or responsibilities of Alpari UK;
  * administrative and judicial authorities when excising laws and regulations Alpari UK is obligated to.

For our website users’ convenience, this Site may provide links to other websites owned, operated and maintained by third parties. These websites provide separate privacy polices than that of Alpari UK’s. For the avoidance of doubt, Alpari UK’s privacy policy applies exclusively to Alpari UK and the Personal Data collected by us. Alpari UK is not responsible for the privacy policies of the third parties’ websites that you link to, nor do we have control over the use or security of information provided by you to those websites or collected by those websites.

Alpari UK may change this Privacy Policy at any time.  You are advised to read this statement each and every time so that you are satisfied with the privacy conditions under which you provide Alpari UK with your personal data.

### Your consent

By accessing the Site, you consent to Alpari UK collecting, maintaining, using and disclosing your Personal Data in accordance with this privacy policy.

### Your rights

The Data Protection Act gives you various rights about your Personal Data, such as accessing and correcting your Personal Data, preventing processing of your Personal Data, preventing unsolicited marketing and so on. Detailed information about your rights under UK Data Protection Act can be found on the website of the United Kingdom Information Commissioner, [www.ico.gov.uk](http://www.ico.gov.uk/).

### Queries

If you have privacy questions which are not answered by this Privacy Policy or any other concerns about how we use your personal data, please write to us ([info@alpari.co.uk](mailto:info@alpari.co.uk)) or contact us [+44 20 7426 2900](tel:442074262900) (Mon-Fri 07:00-22:00 UK time).
